[
    {
        "question": "Stockholm is located along what sea?",
        "answer": "The Baltic Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what province or territory will you find Canada`s tallest mountain?",
        "answer": "Yukon"
    },
    {
        "question": "The point on land closest to the North Pole belongs to what nation?",
        "answer": "Denmark"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Notting Hill road is home to London`s most famous antique market?",
        "answer": "Portobello Road"
    },
    {
        "question": "Until 1790, what was known as Jenkins Hill?",
        "answer": "Capitol Hill"
    },
    {
        "question": "What San Francisco hill is home to a famous colony of wild parrots?",
        "answer": "Telegraph Hill"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to legend, what city was founded on Palatine Hill?",
        "answer": "Rome"
    },
    {
        "question": "About how many islands are in the Stockholm archipelago?",
        "answer": "30,000 -- It is a string of islands in the Baltic Sea. Sweden claims the island chain as part of its territory."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the only person in the U.K. allowed to drive without a license?",
        "answer": "The Queen -- This is because licenses are issued in her name, making her own license rather redundant."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which river forms a border between France and Germany?",
        "answer": "The Rhine"
    },
    {
        "question": "What tunnel connects France and Italy?",
        "answer": "Mont Blanc Tunnel"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city was host to the first official Association football game in 1863?",
        "answer": "London"
    },
    {
        "question": "The State of Washington was originally going to be called what?",
        "answer": "Columbia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US capital city was originally called Le Fleur`s Bluff?",
        "answer": "Jackson"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is Salton Sea fresh water or salt water?",
        "answer": "Salt water"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state has shoreline along the Gulf of Mexico and the Atlantic Ocean?",
        "answer": "Florida"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is famous for its French Quarter?",
        "answer": "New Orleans"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is home to North Cascades National Park?",
        "answer": "Washington"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the two letter postal abbreviation for the state of Delaware?",
        "answer": "DE"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is called the Magnolia State?",
        "answer": "Mississippi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Carson City is the capital of which US state?",
        "answer": "Nevada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is referred to as the `Silver State`?",
        "answer": "Nevada"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the smallest ocean?",
        "answer": "The Arctic Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the geographical term for a ring-shaped coral island?",
        "answer": "Atoll"
    },
    {
        "question": "What language is spoken in the Pacific capital city of Yaren?",
        "answer": "Nauruan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Canadian island was named for the father of Queen Victoria?",
        "answer": "Prince Edward Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two Canadian provinces have capitals named for the same person?",
        "answer": "British Columbia and Saskatchewan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the mainland portion of the province originally called Newfoundland?",
        "answer": "Labrador"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only one of the Great Lakes that has no Canadian waters?",
        "answer": "Lake Michigan"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city would you find the most famous street named `Bourbon Street`?",
        "answer": "New Orleans"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is home to the Great Barrier Reef?",
        "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which ancient site in the mountains of Peru is known as `The Lost City of the Incas`?",
        "answer": "Machu Picchu"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the volcano near Tokyo, Japan called?",
        "answer": "Mount Fuji"
    },
    {
        "question": "What river does the Tower Bridge in London cross?",
        "answer": "Thames"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which river separates Mexico from the US?",
        "answer": "Rio Grande"
    },
    {
        "question": "What cheese is served with a classic Greek salad?",
        "answer": "Feta"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is nicknamed `The Big Peach`?",
        "answer": "Atlanta"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Asian city has an egg-shaped Space Museum?",
        "answer": "Hong Kong"
    },
    {
        "question": "What postal code has Canada Post assigned to Santa Claus`s residence at the North Pole?",
        "answer": "H0H 0H0"
    },
    {
        "question": "Klamath Lake is the largest lake in which US state?",
        "answer": "Oregon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the `Sunflower State`?",
        "answer": "Kansas"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Albemarle Sound is located in what body of water?",
        "answer": "Atlantic Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only country which borders the Black Sea and the Caspian Sea?",
        "answer": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state is the Acadia National Park located?",
        "answer": "Maine"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state is Oral Roberts University located?",
        "answer": "Oklahoma"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state is Gettysburg National Military Park?",
        "answer": "Pennsylvania"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the highest waterfall?",
        "answer": "Angel Falls"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country is Angel Falls located?",
        "answer": "Venezuela"
    },
    {
        "question": "Brisbane is the state capital of which Australian state?",
        "answer": "Queensland"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capitol of Morocco?",
        "answer": "Rabat"
    }
]